ARTSIOM SAUCHUK



JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

WWW.A-SAUCHUK.VERCEL.APP



ABOUT ME

I'm a JavaScript (FE/BE) Developer with more than 1.5 years of experience in developing user interfaces, testing, debugging. Have a proven ability to collaborate effectively with senior developers. Enjoy working with team members to ensure workloads are effectively redirected to bottlenecks. Mentor of the students in The Rolling Scopes School. Dedicated and hard working with internal drive to succeed.



CONTACT

Address: Minsk, BELARUS

Mobile:

+375 29 791 58 36

Telegram:

t.me/hansolo_666

Email:

savchuk799@gmail.com



LANGUAGES

RUSSIAN — NATIVE

ENGLISH — B1



SKILLS

HTML/CSS Jest

JavaScript Webpack

React.JS Git

Node.JS AWS

TypeScript PostgeSQL

Json/REST API MongoDB

JIRA Scrum



EXPERIENCES

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

EPAM SYSTEMS

2022 - NOW

- Development of new user-facing features, optimisation.

- E2E Testing.

- Participation in daily meetings and scrum sessions.

POWER ENGINEER

000 ELECTROSCHIT-SERVICE

2018 - 2021

- Development of electrical circuits.

Project management. Personnel management.

POWER ENGINEER

OOO ARTKA-ENERGO

2017 - 2018

- Electrical installation works.

- Permission obtainment in state structures.



EDUCATION

EPAM SYSTEMS

NODE JS WEB TRAINIG

2022

JS Lab NODE.JS Short Track Course

CERTIFICATE OF WEB TRAINIG

THE ROLLING SCOPES

SCHOOL

REACT 2021Q3 (JAVASCRIPT)

2021

LINK: https://app.rs.school/certificate/ith7gxcc

THE ROLLING SCOPES

SCHOOL

CERTIFICATE OF WEB TRAINIG

2021

JAVASCRIPT/FRONT-END 2021Q1 (JAVASCRIPT) LINK: https://app.rs.school/certificate/2faovg51

BELARUSSIAN NATIONAL TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

TECHNICAL UNIVERS

2012 - 2017

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN POWER ENGINEERING

Faculty: Power Engineering

Speciality: Electric Power Systems and Grids